





Neha Singh Neha Singh Featured Senior Business Analyst seeking roles in IT Project Management, Software Development, Product Policy Configuration, Requirement Gathering, Business Analysis, Use Cases, User Acceptance Testing, API Integration, Credit Operations, IT Operations Current Designation: Senior Business Analyst -IT Total Experience: 11 Year(s) 0 Month(s) Current Company: APAC Financial Services Pvt Ltd., Notice Period: 2 Months Current Location: Mumbai Highest Degree: MBAPGDM [Finance] Pref. Location: Ahmedabad, Mumbai, Pune Functional Area: IT Software - Application Programming / Role: Business Analyst Industry: Banking/Financial Services/Broking Marital Status: Married Key Skills: Senior Business Analyst,IT Project Management,Software Development,Product Policy Configuration, Requirement Gathering, Business Analysis, Use Cases, User Acceptance Testing, API Integration, Credit Operations IT Operations Verified : L Phone Number | Email - id

Last Active: 19-Jan-21

Last Modified: 19-Jan-21

Jump to Section

Work Experience | Education | IT Skills |

# Summary

Offering 10+ years of experience in Credit Operations, IT Operations, Policy and Payables in Banking & financial Services

Abilities in developing, enhancing, and implementing systems for automating banking processes and steering the transition from manual to computerized systems

Effectively contributed to enhancing organizational processes through initiatives geared towards lowering risk, heightening productivity & improving internal controls

Proficiency in monitoring various branch operations and maintaining long-term customer relationships through the provision of high-quality service

In-depth understanding of all processes and systems connected with banking / non-banking industry Possess excellent communication & interpersonal skills

# **Work Experience**

APAC Financial Services Pvt Ltd., as Senior Business Analyst -IT May 2019 to Till Date

Drive all the pending UAT / bugs of miFin system.

UAT of Digital lending system.

Automation of NACH process/Bulk upload.

Solve SQL related queries

Mobile app to be developed for existing customers.

Upgrade the miFin system as per business requirements.

Budgeting vendor cost

Vendor management

Negotiate with various vendors on pricing

Capital First Ltd, as Manager Policy

Mar 2015 to Dec 2016

Policy setup on FinnOne System (All products) Score card implementation for PL, STLAP, TW, UC, AFFORDABLE HOUSING Vendor bills management & provisioning for the month Sales force UAT's (CD / PL cross sell product) Co-ordinate with I.T for timely delivery of UAT's Audit queries Rationalisation of deviations on time to time basis Automating manual deviations FICO implementatation (MIP)

# **Important**

· Using Free CV Search you have access to featured candidate profiles of Naukri. You can browse through the profiles and email the candidates of your choice directly using the email option provided. To prevent misuse of candidate information, contact details and attached resume of the candidates have been withheld

Reliance Capital as Deputy Manager - Credit & IT Jun 2012 to Feb 2015

Steering initiatives for addressing queries on Finnone System (Loan Origination System) Accountable for policy setup and SME System setup

Policy setup includes various retail asset products viz Auto loans, SME, Loan against gold.

Maintenance of LOS master vizuser id maintenance, DSA, SM name, Make, Model, Manufacturer etc. Creation of parameters, condition, rules & deviation.

Handling day-to-day queries of LOS like deviation & eligibility related.

Handling Collection management system.(Finnone system)

^ Back to Top

## **Education**

UG: B.Com (Commerce) from Mumbai University in 2006

PG: MBA/PGDM (Finance) from Institute for Technology and Management (ITM) in 2011

^ Back to Top

## IT Skills

Skill Name	Version	Last Used	Experience
MS OFFICE			
MS ACCESS			

^ Back to Top

## Languages Known

Language	Proficiency	Read	Write	Speak
English	Proficient	✓	✓	✓
Hindi	Proficient	✓	✓	✓
Marathi				

^ Back to Top

# **Affirmative Action**

# **Work Authorization**

Category: General Physically Challenged: No Job Type: Permanent Employment Status: Full time

^ Back to Top

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.

Careers - About Us - Clients - Terms & Conditions - FAQ's - Contact Us - Report a Problem - Site Map - Resources Our Partners: Jeevansathi Matrimonials - ICIClcommunities.org - 99acres - Real Estate In India All rights reserved © 2021 Info Edge India Ltd.